Privacy Policy
==============

_Last updated: August 1, 2019_

1\. Information We Collect
--------------------------

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website, service, and billing. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from customers: Name, Email Address, Credit Card and Other Billing Information

All billing information that we receive from our customers is stored securely with our billing processor. We do not store credit card information locally.

Certain information, such as your IP address and the pages that you visit on the Site are available to us automatically (see the section on Cookies and Tracking for more information). We do not track activities outside of the Ghost Path site.

##### Summary

We need some basic information to create your account and bill you.

2\. Information We Collect About A VPN Session
----------------------------------------------

We do not log any data related to your VPN sessions.

##### Summary

No logs, ever.

3\. Email
---------

Ghost Path will never send marketing email to you unless you specifically opt-in to receive those communications. We will only send you transactional emails, such as welcome emails, payment receipts, etc.

If you do opt-in to marketing emails then we will always provide you with an easy way to unsubscribe in each marketing email that we send you.

We will never sell or rent your email address to a third-party.

##### Summary

No spam, ever.

4\. Sharing Your Information
----------------------------

Ghost Path will neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and we will share your personal information only as described below.

_Ghost Path Personnel:_ Ghost Path personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Ghost Path business.

_Service Providers:_ Ghost Path may use third-party service providers, including but not limited to payment processors and email marketing platforms. We will only share the minimum amount of data needed for the third-party to perform their designated functions.

_Business Transfers:_ In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Ghost Path, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

_Protection of Ghost Path and Others:_ We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Ghost Path, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

##### Summary

We keep your information private.

5\. Keeping Personal Information Secure
---------------------------------------

Your Ghost Path account is password protected. We encrypt passwords before storing them to maximize security. You should also make sure that you keep your password secure.

Ghost Path employees, consultants and contractors may only access your personal information if needed for a specific reason, such as a customer support request. Ghost Path team members, consultants and contractors are trained in our privacy policies and understand that privacy is the top priority.

##### Summary

Don't let others know your password.

6\. How To Contact Ghost Path
-----------------------------

Ghost Path Support is always available. Please send an email to help@ghostpath.com if you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy policy.

##### Summary

Email help@ghostpath.com if you have questions.

7\. Cookies
-----------

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are stored on your device through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Ghost Path cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated.

##### Summary

We need cookies to be able to log you into our site.

8\. Analytics Providers
-----------------------

We may use third-party analytics providers to assist in helping us optimize our site and services. Examples of these third-party providers include but aren't limited to Google Analytics. These providers don't have access to any personally identifiable information.

##### Summary

We use Google Analytics, just like every other website.

9\. Children Under 18
---------------------

Our service is intended for use only by adults over the age of 18. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 and they have entered personal information on our site then please contact help@ghostpath.com immediately so that we can remove that information.

##### Summary

No one under 18 should use Ghost Path.

10\. How To Update Your Personal Information
--------------------------------------------

You are free to update the personal information that we have on file for you by logging into our website. If there is any information that you wish to update that you cannot, or cannot figure out how to, then simply email help@ghostpath.com and we will help you.

##### Summary

Updating your information as is easy as logging into our website.

11\. Changes To This Policy
---------------------------

Ghost Path may, at its sole discretion, update this Privacy policy from time to time. In the event of a change to this Privacy policy we will post a notification on our website.

##### Summary

We might update the Privacy policy, but we'll let you know if we do.

12\. Conditions of Use
----------------------

This Privacy policy, together with our Terms of Service, constitutes the entire agreement between Ghost Path and you. If you visit the Ghost Path website and/or utilize our service then you agree to these policies.

##### Summary

You agree to the Privacy policy and the Terms of Service

###### ghost path

###### Privacy Tools

###### Support

###### renewable energy

Ghost Path runs on 100% Renewable Energy. [See the renewable energy projects we support.](https://climate.stripe.com/9EVKSs)

© 2012 - 2024 Ghost Path, Inc. [Privacy Policy](https://ghostpath.com/privacy) [Terms of Service](https://ghostpath.com/terms)[DMCA](https://ghostpath.com/dmca)
